[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When the white part of the egg is aerate or whipped to a light, fluffy consistency known as soft peaks and stiff peaks what sort of dessert or topping do you have?", "correct_answer": "Meringue", "incorrect_answers": ["Custard", "Ice Cream", "Mustard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A woodcutter chopped down enough trees to have 896 cubic feet of firewood. How many cords did he chop?", "correct_answer": "7", "incorrect_answers": ["6", "4", "5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was the first in-flight meal served?", "correct_answer": "1919", "incorrect_answers": ["1969", "1949", "1959"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Bering Sea is a part of which ocean?", "correct_answer": "The Pacific Ocean", "incorrect_answers": ["The Arctic Ocean", "The Indian Ocean", "The Atlantic Ocean"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these organs has no known function in the human body?", "correct_answer": "appendix", "incorrect_answers": ["tonsils", "uvula", "pineal gland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where were the oldest ears of popcorn found in 1948?", "correct_answer": "Bat Cave, New Mexico", "incorrect_answers": ["Mammoth, Kentucky", "Crystal Cave, California", "Wyandotte Cave, Indiana"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Suppose that an increase in the price of good Y results in an increase in the demand for good X. This phenomenon is an example of which effect in economics?", "correct_answer": "The substitution effect", "incorrect_answers": ["The income effect", "The supply effect", "The demand effect."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays Jonathan E in the 1975 science fiction film Rollerball?", "correct_answer": "James Caan", "incorrect_answers": ["Paul Newman", "Sylvester Stallone", "Arnold Schwarzenegger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Youre crossing Hoover Dam from Nevada into Arizona (USA) during the Winter months (after Oct 31st).  Will you change Time Zones?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how much paper does the average American use in one year?", "correct_answer": "580 pounds", "incorrect_answers": ["One  ton ( 2000 pounds)", "3,400 pounds", "1,500 pounds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Legend has it that MMs were made for what soldiers?", "correct_answer": "American soldiers", "incorrect_answers": ["Spanish soldiers", "French soldiers", "Japanese soldiers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish this Irish saying: If someone is sick turn his bed so that it faces _________.", "correct_answer": "north", "incorrect_answers": ["the TV", "the wall", "a window"]}]